http://www.big4.com.au/terms-and-conditions

BIG4 Holiday Parks Terms and Conditions
This page contains terms and conditions for the following:BIG4 Holiday Parks DisclaimerBIG4 Gift Cards BIG4 Holiday PerksBrand PromiseInternational Site PassGeneral BIG4 Holiday Park Reservations and Tariffs PoliciesBIG4 Privacy PolicyFor a specific BIG4 Holiday Park's terms and conditions please visit the associated park's page
1. BIG4 Holiday Parks DisclaimerBIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia take no responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of, or the representations made by, the content of this site. BIG4 Holiday Parks takes no responsibility for the content of any World Wide Web site that links from this website. Please read the disclaimer.This website contains information provided by BIG4 Member Parks and suppliers. You should be aware that there may be technical inaccuracies, typographical errors, programming bugs or computer viruses in this website or its content.Access to this web site is provided on the condition that:(i) To the full extent permitted by law, BIG4 Holiday Parks will be under no liability to any person in respect of any loss or damage (including consequential loss or damage) which may be suffered or incurred or which may arise directly or indirectly from or in connection with any use of this website or of the information on or accessed through this website for whatever reason (including negligence).(ii) Where any statute implies any term in relation to your use of this website and that statute prohibits any exclusion or modification of that term, then that term is included. However, the liability of BIG4 Holiday Parks for breach of any such term will be limited to negotiating on behalf of the customer with the BIG4 Member Park and supplier.Any information contained within this site about any subject matter whosoever is of a general nature only and is not intended to be complete or definitive. You should obtain professional advice before taking any action in relation to any matter referred to on this site.All BIG4 Holiday Parks are independent member of BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd, the registered owner of the BIG4 Logo. BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd is not the owner of any of the particular BIG4 Holiday Parks. We only facilitate the booking service through the BIG4 website. All bookings are made directly with the individual owner of the BIG4 Holiday Park.Each BIG4 Holiday Park has its own particular terms and conditions. You should request a copy of the terms and conditions of the particular BIG4 Holiday Park at which you intend to stay. These can be found at in the Reservation Terms and Conditions above.BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd makes no warranty or representation as to the fitness for purpose or suitability of any BIG4 Holiday Park or any service provided thereby. While we endeavour to ensure that the information displayed on the BIG4 website and in this form is accurate, as we need to access information from our Member Parks, we are unable to guarantee the accuracy of the information.BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd accepts no responsibility or liability in relation to any claims, loses, damages, or expenses howsoever arising, whether direct or indirect or consequential, except as required by statute, relating to:(a) facilitating any booking; or(b) a breach by any person (including the individual proprietor of the BIG4 Holiday Park at which you intend to stay) of these terms or the terms and conditions of the particular BIG4 Holiday Park; or(c) otherwise in relation to reservation, or stay, at a particular BIG4 Holiday Park.These terms and conditions are governed by the laws of Victoria. References to "we" and "us" relate to BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd, ABN 50 006 437 038.We recommend that you carefully read these conditions and the terms and conditions for the BIG4 Holiday Park chosen by you.For further information please direct correspondence toBIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty LtdPO Box 543Camberwell VIC 3124
2. BIG4 Gift Cards - Terms & Conditions1. Both the BIG4 Gift Cards (“Card”) and the BIG4 Electronic Gift Vouchers (“Voucher”) are issued by BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd ABN 50 006 437 038 (“BIG4”), and both the Card and Voucher remain the property of BIG4. By purchasing, redeeming or attempting to redeem a Card or Voucher, you accept and agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions; and acknowledge that you have read and understood our Privacy Policy (available by calling 1300 738 044 or here).2. Cards or Vouchers may be purchased for any whole dollar denomination amount, with a minimum of $50 (AUD) and a maximum of $4,999(AUD). The value of a Card or Voucher cannot be changed after purchase.3. Cards or Vouchers are redeemable at any participating BIG4 Holiday Park location. The location of participating BIG4 Holiday Parks may change from time to time and an up-to-date list of the participating parks is available on www.big4.com.au (“Web Site”). Cards or Vouchers can only be used to purchase accommodation and selected other items at BIG4 Holiday Parks (check at each park for details). Redemption for accommodation is subject to availability. Once the Card or Voucher has been redeemed, then the terms and conditions of the relevant park will apply.4. Your Card and/or Voucher must be presented at the time of payment to be redeemed. If your purchase exceeds the remaining amount on your Card or Voucher, you must pay the excess using a different payment method. The Card or Voucher may be used in part or in full, and any remaining balance can be applied towards subsequent purchases.5. Cards or Vouchers cannot be used to obtain cash advances, refunded, on-sold, or redeemed or exchanged for cash.6. Treat your Card or Voucher like cash. If a Card or Voucher is lost, stolen or destroyed, you must advise BIG4 immediately. In such circumstances, BIG4 may cancel and reissue a Card or Voucher provided it is comfortably satisfied that you are the rightful holder of the Card or Voucher, and you are able to provide adequate proof of identity. BIG4 may, at its sole discretion, refuse to replace any Card or Voucher.7. Cards and Vouchers must be redeemed within 36 months of issue (“Validity Period”). Any Card or Voucher not used within the Validity Period will be void and of no value. Any unused value will not be refunded.8. Cards will generally be delivered by express post within 10 working days of purchase (within Australia only). Subject to clause 6, BIG4 will not liable for any Gift Cards which are lost or damaged in the post. The Purchaser is responsible for informing BIG4 of the correct delivery details.9. Vouchers are delivered via e-mail. It is the purchaser’s responsibility to enter the correct email address for the voucher to be sent to. If the voucher does not arrive with 24 hours of purchase, it is the purchaser’s responsibility to contact BIG4 to arrange an alternative method of delivery.10. Postage charges apply as follows for Cards;A charge of $6.00 will apply for BIG4 Club Members who provide their valid BIG4 Membership Identification Number;For all other purchasers a charge of $10.00 will apply11. In the event of a query or a dispute in relation to your Card or Voucher, or any accommodation purchased with the Card or Voucher, you can contact BIG4 on 1300 738 044 or in writing at BIG4 Holiday Parks, PO Box 543 Camberwell VIC 3124 or via our contact page12. To the extent permitted by law, BIG4 will not be liable to you for any loss or damage (whether direct or consequential), nor be in default under these Terms & Conditions, for failure to observe or perform any of our obligations under these Terms & Conditions for any reason or cause which could not, with reasonable diligence, be controlled or prevented. These causes include acts of God, acts of nature, acts or omissions of government or their agencies, strikes or other industrial action, fire, flood, storm, riots, power shortages or failures, sudden and unexpected system failure or disruption by war or sabotage, and other acts or omissions of third parties.13. BIG4 reserves the right to change any of the terms contained in these Terms & Conditions at any time where the change is required:To add or remove participating parks and/or where the Card or Voucher may be redeemed;To add or remove goods or services which may be purchased with the Card or Voucher;For infrastructural, systems, administrative or operational reasons or to prevent the occurrence of fraud or other unlawful or unacceptable conduct;To comply with any contract, law, regulation or statute or order or judgment of any court, tribunal or other body having competent jurisdiction; orWhere we, acting reasonably, consider that it will not be to your detriment.Changes to these Terms and Conditions will be available on our Web Site, at participating parks, or by contacting 1300 738 044
3. Perks Membership Terms & ConditionsBIG4 Holiday Perks Membership Program Terms and ConditionsEligibility for Benefits(a) Subject to clauses 1(b) and 1(c), BIG4 Holiday Perks are available to BIG4 Members with Perks+ Membership or VIPerks Membership who have paid their respective Membership fees in full at the time of electing to use the relevant benefit.(b) Permanent Residents are only eligible to receive BIG4 Holiday Perks at any BIG4 Park that they do not ordinarily reside in, or maintain a permanent site at.(c) Any BIG4 Member with a VIPerks Membership who stays in a BIG4 Park for more than 28 consecutive nights will receive a 10% uncapped discount for first 28 nights.Membership and BenefitsIndividuals are eligible for BIG4 Membership by completing the application form available on the Website or at any BIG4 Park or by sending a postal application obtained at a BIG4 Park and paying the required fee (where applicable).BIG4 offers three levels of Membership:(a)Perks Membership(i)Perks is a free Membership level provided automatically to email subscribers to the Website and / or BIG4 Account holders.(ii)BIG4 Members with Perks Membership receive access to pre-release holiday deals at BIG4 Holiday Parks.(iii)For the avoidance of doubt, BIG4 Members with Perks Membership are not entitled to any BIG4 Holiday Perks.(b)Perks+ MembershipPerks+ Membership costs $50 which must be paid upon becoming a BIG4 Member with Perks+ Membership. BIG4 Members with Perks+ Membership receive:(i)a 10% discount on BIG4 Accommodation up to the value of $50 per stay;(ii)benefits provided by BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partners;(iii)a minimum of 1 In-Park Perk during every stay when booked directly through a BIG4 Holiday Park or on the Website; and(iv)certain discounts applying to accommodation available at Affiliate Parks (as indicated on the Website) from time to time.(c)VIPerks MembershipVIPerks Membership is a free upgrade offered to BIG4 Members with Perks+ Membership once such members have qualified for VIPerks Membership in accordance with clause 2.3.BIG4 Members with VIPerks Membership receive:(i)a 10% discount on BIG4 Accommodation for any stay up to a maximum of 28 consecutive nights (with no cap on the total dollar value of that discount);(ii)benefits provided by BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partners;(iii)a minimum of 1 In-Park Perk during each stay when the stay is booked directly through a BIG4 Holiday Park or on the Website; and(iv)certain discounts applying to accommodation available at Affiliate Parks (as indicated on the Website).Qualifying for a VIPerks Membership(a)A BIG4 Member with Perks+ Membership will be upgraded free of charge to a VIPerks Membership once they have:(i)exceeded a spend amount of $4,000 (including GST and discounts) on BIG4 Accommodation (Qualifying Amount); and(ii)made and completed 2 Bookings at 2 different BIG4 Parks (each a Relevant Booking),within 2 years of having obtained a valid Perks+ Membership (VIPerks Membership Criteria).(b)BIG4 may also offer complimentary upgrades to VIPerks Membership at any time, at its own discretion.(c)In order for a VIPerks Membership upgrade to be offered to a BIG4 Member with Perks+ Membership, the BIG4 Member must spend the Qualifying Amount at one or more Relevant Bookings and when making a Relevant Booking, the BIG4 Member must:(i)provide his/her Membership number;(ii)ensure the name on the Relevant Booking matches the name on his/her Membership Card;(iii)ensure his/her Perks+ Membership is valid at the time of check-out with respect to the Relevant Booking;(iv)ensure the Relevant Booking does not overlap with another Booking that has already been applied towards a VIPerks Membership upgrade;(v)ensure the Relevant Booking period does not exceed 28 days; and(vi)make the Relevant Booking directly with either a BIG4 Holiday Park or on the Website.(d)For the avoidance of doubt:(i)the stay associated with any Booking must have reached check-out date and otherwise completed before that Booking becomes a Relevant Booking;(ii)cancelled Bookings will not accrue towards, or be counted in respect of, a VIPerks Membership upgrade; and(iii)any Bookings which have not been paid for in full will not accrue towards a VIPerks Membership upgrade.(e)Any Booking applied towards a VIPerks Membership accrual will expire 2 years after the check-out date if the VIPerks Membership has not qualified for VIPerks at that time.Booking HistoryBIG4 Members can access their Booking History via their BIG4 Account on the Website, to monitor and determine whether their Bookings have met the VIPerks Membership Criteria and can accrue towards earning a VIPerks Membership upgrade.In the Booking History, each Booking made will display as one of the following:Pending – will count towards a VIPerks Membership upgrade once the BIG4 Member has checked out;Applied – counts towards earning a VIPerks Membership upgrade in the future;Allocated – already counted towards the current VIPerks Membership upgrade;Invalid – this Booking does not count towards a VIPerks Membership upgrade; andExpired – Booking was checked out over 2 years ago and no longer counts towards a VIPerks Membership upgrade.If a BIG4 Member wishes to make any enquiries with regards to his/her Booking History (including, without limitation, rectifying any perceived inaccuracies in the Booking History), they may call the BIG4 National Support office line 1300 738 004.BIG4 does not guarantee the accuracy of a Booking History.Once a VIPerks Membership upgrade has been applied(a)If a BIG4 Member with Perks+ Membership is upgraded to VIPerks Membership in accordance with these Terms, then the Relevant Bookings which were applied to obtain such an upgrade will have the term "Allocated" displayed next to them in the BIG4 Member's Booking History and $4,000 will be deducted from the accrued spend balance in the BIG4 Member's Booking History immediately after reaching the VIPerks Membership level.(b)A VIPerks Membership upgrade is applied for 2 years.(c)If a BIG4 Member with a Perks+ Membership qualifies for a VIPerks Membership upgrade:(i)within 12 months of obtaining a Perks+ Membership or renewing a Perks+ Membership, the Expiry Date will be extended to a date which is 2 years from the date of the upgrade; or(ii)between 12 – 24 months of obtaining a Perks+ Membership or renewing a Perks+ Membership:(A)the Expiry Date will remain unchanged; and(B)upon renewal of the Membership by paying the $50 fee prior to the Expiry Date, the BIG4 Member will automatically renew as a BIG4 Member with VIPerks Membership for a 2 year period.If a BIG4 Member fails to renew the Membership before the Expiry Date in accordance with clause 4, the BIG4 Member loses the right to renew as a BIG4 Member with VIPerks Membership and the accrual of Relevant Bookings and spend balance will be reset to nil.Membership PeriodSubject to these Terms:(a)Perks Membership continues for as long as the BIG4 Member is an email subscriber to the Website and/or a BIG4 Account holder; and(b)Perks+ Membership and VIPerks Membership each last for a period of 2 years.Membership Cards(a)BIG4 Members with Perks+ or VIPerks Membership can opt to receive a physical or digital Membership Card at the time of becoming a BIG4 Member with the requisite level of Membership. In the absence of any election by the BIG4 Member, a physical Membership Card will be provided.(b)All physical Membership Cards remain the property of BIG4. The BIG4 Member must exercise reasonable care in having and maintaining a physical Membership Card and return or destroy it at the request of BIG4.(c)Should a BIG4 Member have a reasonable basis to require a replacement of a physical Membership Card, BIG4 will use reasonable endeavours to cancel the existing Membership Card and issue a replacement card to the relevant BIG4 Member. Any physical Membership Card replacement will be sent to the BIG4 Member's address registered to their BIG4 Account.(d)A digital Membership Card may be obtained from a BIG4 Park and is available to print from the BIG4 Membership portal on the Website (www.big4.com.au/perks) at any time.(e)There is no difference between the value and benefits attached to a physical Membership Card and a digital Membership Card.(f)For the avoidance of doubt, a physical Membership Card is not a credit card, EFTPOS card or any other card giving rise to the access of cash.Membership Renewal and Cancellation(a)Memberships can be renewed either via the Website, at a BIG4 Park or by sending a postal renewal application form and paying the required fee.(b)Memberships must be renewed as indicated below for each Membership level before the Expiry Date in order to retain the existing level of Membership and the accrual of Relevant Bookings and spend balance made towards earning VIPerks Membership.(c)Failing to renew before the Expiry Date will reset the accrual of Relevant Bookings and spend balance towards a VIPerks upgrade to nil and will result in any Membership level being downgraded to Perks Membership.(d)BIG4 Members with Perks+ Membership or VIPerks Membership can opt to receive a physical or digital Membership Card upon renewal. In the absence of any election by the BIG4 Member, a physical Membership Card will be provided.(e)BIG4 does not take any responsibility in any potential delays or losses of cheques or any other payments methods when a BIG4 Member has chosen to send a postal renewal application form. This includes, without limitation, the loss of cheques, intercepted mail with malicious intent and delays in processing the Membership renewal which pass the relevant Expiry Date.Perks Membership(a)BIG4 Members with Perks Membership do not need to renew their Membership as this Membership level is free and will continue until it is cancelled in accordance with clause 4.1(c).(b)If a BIG4 Member has Perks Membership, the BIG4 Member can upgrade at any time in order to have Perks+ Membership at a cost of $50 for 2 years.(c)If a BIG4 Member has Perks Membership and wishes to cancel his/her Membership, he/she can unsubscribe from the Website and/or deactivate their BIG4 Account at any time by contacting the BIG4 National Support office line 1300 738 004. Such cancellation will occur automatically.Perks+ Membership(a)A BIG4 Member with Perks+ Membership can renew their Membership by paying the renewal fee of $50 before the Expiry Date.(b)Following renewal of Perks+ Membership:(i)the new Membership Period will commence immediately following the Expiry Date of the previous Membership Period for another 2 year period;(ii)Relevant Bookings with the term "Applied" displayed next to them in the BIG4 Member's Booking History and the spend balance will continue to accrue towards a VIPerks Membership upgrade and will expire 2 years from the date each Relevant Booking was checked out; and(iii)the BIG4 Member will retain the same Membership number.(c)If a BIG4 Member wishes to cancel his/her Perks+ Membership, he/she should not renew the Perks+ Membership prior to the Expiry Date, and unsubscribe from the Website and/or deactivate his/her BIG4 Account at any time by contacting the BIG4 National Support office line 1300 738 004. Such cancellation will occur automatically.VIPerks Membership(a)Subject to clause 2.5(c)(ii), a BIG4 Member with VIPerks Membership must qualify for a VIPerks Membership renewal before the Expiry Date. In order to qualify for such renewal the VIPerks Membership Criteria must be fulfilled.(b)Subject to clause 2.5(c)(ii), a BIG4 Member with VIPerks Membership can renew their VIPerks Membership by (i) paying the renewal fee of $50 before the Expiry Date and (ii) meeting the VIPerks Membership Criteria.(c)Where a BIG4 Member qualifies to renew its VIP Membership and renews its VIPerks Membership in accordance with clause 4.3(b):(i)the renewal period commences the day after the Expiry Date of the previous Membership Period for a further 2 year period;(ii)the Relevant Bookings taken into account in fulfilling the VIP Membership Criteria will have the term "Allocated" displayed next to them and $4,000 will be deducted from the accrued spend balance, in the BIG4 Member's Booking History immediately after renewal;(iii)Relevant Bookings with the term "Applied" displayed next to them in the BIG4 Member's Booking History and the remaining spend balance which was not taken into account in fulfilling the VIP Membership Criteria will remain unchanged until they reach the expiry date of 2 years from the date each Relevant Booking was checked out; and(iv)the BIG4 Member will retain the same Membership number.(d)If a BIG4 Member with VIPerks Membership has not fulfilled the VIPerks Membership Criteria in order to qualify for VIPerks Membership renewal before the Expiry Date but wishes to continue maintaining a BIG4 Membership then:(i)either (A) on payment of the $50 renewal fee, the BIG4 Member's Membership will become a Perks+ Membership, or (B) in the absence of the $50 renewal fee payment, the BIG4 Member's Membership will become a Perks Membership;(ii)the new Membership Period will commence immediately following the Expiry Date of the previous Membership Period;(iii)Relevant Bookings with the term "Applied" displayed next to them in the BIG4 Member's Booking History and the remaining spend balance will remain unchanged until they reach the expiry date of 2 years from the date the Relevant Booking was checked out; and(iv)the BIG4 Member will retain the same Membership number.Member Disqualification(a)BIG4 reserves the right, at any time, to verify the validity of BIG4 Members (including their personal details), their Booking History and to disqualify any BIG4 Member who tampers or appears to have tampered with their account balance, including but not limited to, use of software or any other mechanical means that allows a BIG4 Member to misrepresent the actual accrued Bookings towards a VIPerks Membership upgrade. Digital errors and/or omissions may be accepted or rejected at BIG4's sole discretion.(b)If the Program is interfered with in any way by a BIG4 Member or any other person (including but not limited to technical difficulties, unauthorised intervention or fraud) BIG4 reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to disqualify any BIG4 Member (or any other person), terminate the Terms with respect to that BIG4 Member or refuse an application for Membership from any such person.(c) BIG4 wants guests to feel safe and respected at BIG4 parks. BIG4 reserves the right to disqualify any BIG4 Member where:(i) BIG4 has reasonable grounds to believe that the BIG4 Member has engaged in behaviour at a BIG4 park that is anti-social, such as:(A) behaviour that harms or has the potential to harm the safety and well-being of other people at the BIG4 park;(B) engaging in behaviour that violates the basic rights of another person (including BIG4 staff, guests or visitors) at the BIG4 park;(C) engaging in behaviour that is overtly and intentionally aggressive or hostile to others (including BIG4 staff, guests or visitors) at the BIG4 park; and(D) engaging in behaviour that is contrary to prevailing norms for social conduct and which behaviour could foreseeably harm another person (physically, mentally or emotionally) that is at the BIG4 park; or(ii) BIG4 has reasonable grounds to believe that the BIG4 Member has engaged in behaviour at a BIG4 park that is morally repugnant, including but not limited to engaging in racist taunts or sexual harassment; and(iii) BIG4 has reasonable grounds to believe that the BIG4 Member has engaged in behaviour at a BIG4 park that could foreseeably lead to that BIG4 Member being arrested and/or charged with a criminal offence and BIG4, in its sole discretion believe that the BIG4 Member could pose a threat of any kind to BIG4 staff, guests and visitors.BIG4 Holiday PerksPerks+ and VIPerks Membership Accommodation SavingsBIG4 Members with either Perks+ Membership or VIPerks Membership are offered a discount on BIG4 Accommodation (see clause 2.2) (Membership Saving). Obtaining the Membership Saving is subject to the conditions described below:(a)Membership Savings are not available to be used in conjunction with any other discount, promotion or package offered by BIG4, a BIG4 Holiday Park or other third party with respect to accommodation.(b)The Membership Saving is for 1 site or 1 cabin per stay at a BIG4 Holiday Park, being:(i)Perks+ Membership - a 10% discount up to a value of $50 per stay; The changes to the discount cap from $40 to $50 for Perks+ members will only apply to new bookings made after 19 June 2018 and(ii)VIPerks Membership - a 10% discount per stay for the first 28 consecutive nights (with no cap on the total dollar value of that discount).(c)The Membership Saving may be claimed at any BIG4 Holiday Park.(d)To obtain the Membership Saving:(i)Bookings must be made directly with the relevant BIG4 Holiday Park at which BIG4 Accommodation is sought or via the Website.(ii)the Booking must be made in the name of the BIG4 Member;(iii)the BIG4 Member in whose name the BIG4 Accommodation is booked must also quote his/her valid BIG4 Membership number as printed on the Membership Card at the time of check-in.(e)For the avoidance of doubt, Bookings made through agents or other intermediaries such as third party booking sites are not eligible for the Membership Saving.(f)BIG4 does not guarantee the availability of any BIG4 accommodation at any time or location to any BIG4 Member (or any other person).In-Park PerksBIG4 Members with either Perks+ Membership or VIPerks Membership are offered In-Park Perks during stays at BIG4 Holiday Parks. The following terms apply to obtaining any In-Park Perks:(a)In-Park Perks (if applicable) can be found on the Park Overview page on the Website.(b)In-Park Perks can be seasonal and the type of In-Park Perk available (if any) is at the discretion of the BIG4 Park.(c)In-Park Perks can only be redeemed once per stay and will be provided to the person who is named on the Membership Card.(d)In-Park Perks must be arranged directly with the BIG4 Park the BIG4 Member is staying at.(e)In-Park Perks can be updated at any time and without prior notice.(f)In-Park Perks are not transferrable or redeemable for cash.(g)In making a Booking at a BIG4 Park, the BIG4 Member will be required to agree to the terms and conditions which apply to the relevant BIG4 Park (Park Terms) and the Park Terms may include terms which relate to obtaining, using, redeeming or otherwise accessing any In-Park Perk. The Park Terms are at the discretion of the operator of the relevant BIG4 Park.(h)BIG4 does not guarantee the availability of any In-Park Perk at any time or location to any BIG4 Member (or any other person).(i)In-park Perks can be substituted at any-time if the listed in-park Perk is unavailable for any reason.BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partners(a)Benefits are also available to BIG4 Members with Perks+ Membership and VIPerks Membership from BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partners (Partner Benefits).(b)Partner Benefits can be found on the Website.(c)To claim Partner Benefits from BIG4 Holiday Perks Partners, the BIG4 Member must present a valid Membership Card to the BIG4 Holiday Perks Partner at the time of purchase of the Partner Benefit. If the transaction is being made by phone or via the internet, the BIG4 Member or representative must provide details of the BIG4 Member's Membership Card to the relevant BIG4 Holiday Perks Partner at the time of purchase.(d)Partner Benefits (if any) offered by a BIG4 Holiday Perks Partner are subject to availability and any terms and conditions determined by the BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partner which are available on the Website.(e)Each BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partner may change, cancel or vary their offer of Partner Benefits to BIG4 Members without notice. Any such change will not impact any confirmed purchase of a Partner Benefit by a BIG4 Member.(f)BIG4 does not guarantee the availability of any Partner Benefit promoted by or in connection with a BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partner.(g)BIG4 may receive a payment from the BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partner in connection with the promotion of the Partner Benefit or its redemption by a BIG4 Member. Any such payment will be advised to you as part of the Partner Benefits terms and conditions.BIG4 Guarantee(a)BIG4 Members with Perks+ or VIPerks Membership receive the benefit of a money back guarantee as described in this clause 7.(b)If a BIG4 Member with Perks+ or VIPerks Membership is not fully satisfied with the facilities or service of a BIG4 Holiday Park within 1 hour of check-in at the relevant BIG4 Accommodation (and notifies the relevant BIG4 Park in accordance with clause7(c)), the cost of BIG4 Accommodation will be cheerfully refunded.(c)To receive a refund under this clause 7, BIG4 Park reception must be notified within 1 hour of check-in that the BIG4 Accommodation is unsatisfactory. Guests must also check out of the BIG4 Park at that time.BIG4 Member AcknowledgementIn accepting these Terms, each BIG4 Member acknowledges that:(a)each BIG4 Holiday Park (and consequently, the relevant BIG4 Accommodation) is operated by a franchisee pursuant to a franchise right granted by BIG4;(b)each BIG4 Holiday Perks Partner is an independent contractor who has no other relationship with BIG4, and that each BIG4 Holiday Perks Partner is not permitted to make any representation on behalf of, and is unable to bind, BIG4;(c)BIG4 Membership is personal to the BIG4 Member and is not transferable, assignable or refundable;(d)BIG4 Membership cannot be converted into cash; and(e)there is a strict limit of 1 BIG4 Membership per person.Changes to the ProgramChange of Benefits(a)BIG4 may make any changes to the Program, including changing these Terms, the Membership Savings or the BIG4 Holiday Perks Partners at any time.(b)BIG4 will advise BIG4 Members of all changes to these Terms and request their acceptance of the amended Terms at least 3 months' in advance of such changes taking effect.(c)If any BIG4 Member does not accept any proposed changes to the Terms, such BIG4 Member may terminate the Terms with respect to his/her Membership and the Membership itself, without liability, by providing written notice of such termination to BIG4.Termination or Suspension of Program(a)BIG4 may cancel, terminate, modify or suspend the Program at any time and for any reason.(b)Subject to clause 9.2(c), if BIG4 chooses to end or suspend the Program, BIG4 will give at least 3 months' written notice to BIG4 Members of such termination or suspension. In such circumstances:(i)all confirmed Bookings will be fulfilled by BIG4 at the discounted rates offered to BIG4 Members;(ii)BIG4 Members with either Perks+ or VIPerks Membership who have not received BIG4 Holiday Perks up to a value of $50 during the current Membership Period will have their Membership fee refunded in full; and(iii)for the avoidance of doubt, BIG4 Members with either Perks+ or VIPerks Membership who have received BIG4 Holiday Perks up to a value of $50 or more during the current Membership Period will not receive a refund,and in any case, neither BIG4 nor any BIG4 Park is liable to any person for any cost, liability, claim or expense arising as a result of cancellation or termination of the Program.(c)If BIG4 ceases to operate a holiday park franchise for any reason, the Program will cease immediately and:(i)BIG4 will provide all BIG4 Members with written notice of the termination of the holiday park franchise and the Program within 7 Business Days of such decision being made (Termination Date);(ii)all confirmed Bookings made with respect to stays [commencing on the Termination Date until such time as the holiday park franchise ceases to be operated by BIG4 (or 12 months from the Termination Date, whichever occurs sooner)] will be fulfilled by BIG4 at the discounted rates offered to BIG4 Members;(iii)BIG4 will not accept any further Bookings to be made following the date of the notice referred to in clause 9.2(c)(i);(iv)BIG4 Members with either Perks+ or VIPerks Membership who have not received BIG4 Holiday Perks up to a value of $50 during the current Membership Period will have their Membership fee refunded in full; and(v)for the avoidance of doubt, BIG4 Members with either Perks+ or VIPerks Membership who have received BIG4 Holiday Perks up to a value of $50 or more during the current Membership Period will not receive a refund,and in any case, neither BIG4 nor any BIG4 Park is liable to any person for any cost, liability, claim or expense arising as a result of cancellation or termination of the Program.(d)If an individual does not agree to abide by, or accept these Terms, they must not apply for, nor maintain any Membership.Collection of InformationBIG4 collects and uses Personal Information in accordance with its Privacy Policy and Privacy Law. In addition, BIG4 collects an individual's Personal Information from that individual's BIG4 Membership application, any revisions of that information made by or on behalf of the BIG4 Member, any Bookings made by a BIG4 Member where the BIG4 Member's Membership number is used and from BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partners when BIG4 Members deal with them in connection with their BIG4 Membership. BIG4 collects that Personal Information to conduct and administer the Program, as well as processing Bookings, conducting research about the Program and developing and marketing goods and services. BIG4 may, for this purpose, disclose such information to third parties, including but not limited to analytics providers, technology solution providers, data storage and processing providers and marketing and digital agencies for the sole purpose for which it was collected. Please note that Personal Information may be transferred outside of Australia to the United States, for the sole purpose for which it was collected. If the information requested is not provided, the individual may not participate in the Program or receive the benefits otherwise available under the Program. By participating in the Program, unless otherwise advised by the individual, each individual also agrees that BIG4 may use their Personal Information, for profiling and research.BIG4 Members have the right to access their Personal Information held by BIG4 and to request that their Personal Information be corrected, updated, or deleted. To exercise this right or to raise a formal complaint concerning a breach of Privacy Law, please contact BIG4 via our contact page or via our postal address PO BOX 543, Camberwell, Victoria, 3124 Australia or by calling 1300 738 044. BIG4 is an entity covered by the NDB (Notifiable Data Breach) Scheme and all BIG4 security incident response activities must act accordingly to NDB provisions. BIG4 will notify the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner of any data breach covered by the NDB Scheme.BIG4 may update its privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.LiabilityAny representation, warranty, condition, guarantee or undertaking that would be implied in these Terms by legislation, common law, equity, trade, custom or usage is excluded to the fullest extent permitted by Law.Nothing in these Terms excludes, restricts or modifies any consumer guarantee, right or remedy conferred on a BIG4 Member by the Australian Consumer Law in Schedule 2 of the Competition and Consumer Act 2010 (Cth) or any other applicable Law that cannot be excluded, restricted or modified by agreement.To the fullest extent permitted by Law, BIG4's liability to a BIG4 Member for a breach of a non-excludable guarantee referred to in clause 11.2 is limited, at BIG4's option, to, in the case of services, any one or more of the following:(a)the supplying of the services again; or(b)the payment of the cost of having the services supplied again.Subject to clauses 11.1 and 11.2, neither BIG4, nor its officers, employees or agents shall be liable to any BIG4 Member for:(a)any tax liability incurred by a BIG4 Member in connection with this Program;(b)any loss or liability resulting from technical errors or issues associated with crediting Booking History onto a BIG4 Account;(c)any loss or liability resulting from communication to any BIG4 Member that is late, lost or misdirected for any reason, including, but not limited to, spam filters operating on a BIG4 Member's email account, being unsubscribed or other system configuration problems;(d)any loss or liability resulting from problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer online systems, servers or providers, computer equipment, software, technical problems or traffic congestion on the internet or at any website or intranet site, or any combination thereof, including (but not limited to) any injury or damage to a BIG4 Member's or any other person's computer related to or resulting from participation in or downloading any materials in the Program.Subject to this clause 11 and to the maximum extent permitted by Law, neither party (Party 1) is liable to the other party (Party 2) or to any other person for:(a)any loss or damage of any kind caused by or resulting from any act or omission of Party 1 or any of its employees, agents or contractors in connection with these Terms, other than loss or damage directly arising from the negligence or wilful misconduct of Party 1 or its officers, employees or agents; or(b)any loss of profits or anticipated profits, economic loss, loss of business opportunity, loss or damage resulting from wasted management time or any special, incidental, indirect or other consequential loss or damage, even if notified of the possibility of that potential loss or damage and irrespective of whether it is due to negligence, breach of contract or any other cause.For the avoidance of doubt, BIG4 does not provide any warranties, guarantees or representations, express or implied, with respect to the Membership Savings, In-Park Perks and Partner Benefits (together, the Benefits), as the Benefits are provided by independent suppliers. Accordingly, nothing in these Terms has any impact on any warranties, guarantees or representations (express or implied) provided by such independent suppliers with regards to the Benefits.Dispute resolutionIf a dispute arises between BIG4 and a BIG4 Member out of or in connection with these Terms, including its construction, effect, the rights and obligations of the parties, the performance, breach, rescission or termination of these Terms, the entitlement of any party to damages or compensation (whether for breach of contract, tort or any other cause of action) or the amount of that entitlement (Dispute), the party claiming that a Dispute has arisen must give the other party a notice containing particulars of the Dispute (Dispute Notice).During the period of 5 Business Days from the date that the Dispute Notice is given, or any longer period agreed in writing by BIG4 and the BIG4 Member (Initial Period), each of the parties must use its reasonable endeavours and act in good faith to resolve the Dispute by discussion and negotiation.If the parties are unable to resolve the Dispute within the Initial Period, the Dispute must be referred to the managing director (or their nominee) of BIG4 to resolve with the BIG4 Member. The parties must:(a)meet promptly (and in any event within 5 Business Days) after the Dispute is referred to them; and(b)use their reasonable endeavours and act in good faith in an attempt to resolve the Dispute within 5 Business Days after the Dispute is referred to them or any longer period agreed in writing by the parties.If the managing director of BIG4 and the BIG4 Member have been unable to resolve the Dispute within the period referred to in clause 12.3, then the parties must submit the Dispute to mediation administered by the Australian Dispute Centre (ADC) in accordance with the ADC Commercial Mediation Guidelines (Rules), which Rules are taken to be incorporated into these Terms.If a Mediator is appointed under clause 12.4, each party must:(a)pay its own costs of complying with this clause 12 and the costs of the Mediator and any other costs of complying with this clause 12 must be shared equally by the parties; and(b)continue to perform their obligations under these Terms while the Dispute is being resolved.No party may commence any judicial proceedings in relation to the Dispute unless:(a)it has complied with any obligation on it under this clause 12;(b)those proceedings are commenced for the purpose of enforcing this clause 12 or to seek interlocutory relief; or(c)following the procedures in clauses 12.1 to 12.4 would mean that a limitation period for a cause of action arising from or relating to the Dispute will expire.No disparagementBIG4 and BIG4 Members agree not to discredit or disparage each other, in relation to or in connection with any Dispute that may arise between them, these Terms, the Program or any other matter contemplated by these Terms.GeneralThese Terms contain the entire understanding between the parties concerning the subject matter of these Terms and supersedes, terminates and replaces all prior agreements and communications between the parties concerning that subject matter. Each party acknowledges that, except as expressly stated in these Terms, it has not relied on any representation, warranty, undertaking or statement made by or on behalf of another party in relation to these Terms or its subject matter.Any provision of these Terms which is invalid in any jurisdiction must, in relation to that jurisdiction, be:(a)read down to the minimum extent necessary to achieve its validity, if applicable; and(b)severed from these Terms in any other case,without invalidating or affecting the remaining provisions of these Terms or the validity of that provision in any other jurisdiction.A BIG4 Member cannot assign or otherwise deal with the benefit of these Terms without the prior written consent of BIG4.The relationship between a BIG4 Member and BIG4 for all purposes of these Terms is that of service provider and customer. These Terms are to be construed in every respect to give effect to this independence. Nothing in these Terms may be construed as creating a relationship of partnership, of principal and agent or of trustee and beneficiary.A failure to exercise, a delay in exercising or partially exercising any power, right or remedy conferred on a party by or in respect of these Terms does not operate as a waiver by that party of the power, right or remedy. A single or partial exercise of any power, right or remedy does not preclude a further exercise of it or the exercise of any other power, right or remedy. A waiver of a breach does not operate as a waiver of any other breach.These Terms are governed by and must be construed in accordance with the Laws of Victoria, Australia. The parties submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Victoria and the Commonwealth of Australia in respect of all matters arising out of or relating to these Terms, its performance or subject matter.DefinitionsUnless the context otherwise requires in these terms and conditions:Affiliate Park means a park which is listed on the Website as an "affiliate" park and is not a BIG4 Park;BIG4 means BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd ACN 006 437 038;BIG4 Accommodation means the accommodation facilities contained in, or operated as part of, any BIG4 Holiday Park;BIG4 Account is an account established by a BIG4 Member on the Website;BIG4 Holiday Park or BIG4 Park means a holiday park operated by a franchisee of BIG4 as listed on the Website;BIG4 Holiday Perks means the benefits which are available to BIG4 Members who have a Perks+ Membership or VIPerks Membership;BIG4 Holiday Perks Benefits Partner means a Person who has agreed with BIG4 to make an offer of benefits to BIG4 Members for the purposes of clause 6.3;BIG4 Member means an individual whose application to join the Program has been accepted by BIG4;Booking means a booking made by a BIG4 Member to stay at BIG4 Accommodation for the purposes of visiting a BIG4 Park;Booking History is the history of Bookings for each BIG4 Member, which includes details of the status of each Booking and whether or not a Booking provided any benefit to the BIG4 Member for the purposes of obtaining a VIPerks Membership (a copy of which each BIG4 Member can access through the Website);Business Day means a day that is not a Saturday, Sunday, public holiday or bank holiday in Victoria, Australia;Expiry Date means the expiry date of the Membership as indicated on the BIG4 Account and on the digital Membership Card;In-Park Perks mean any specific benefits which are offered at a BIG4 Park and which are unique to the facilities and services of each specific BIG4 Park. They may include, without limitation, early check-in, late check-out, free WI-FI, go-cart hire discount or mini-golf discount;Law means:(a)principles of law or equity established by decisions of Australian courts;(b)statutes, regulations or by-laws of the Commonwealth of Australia, or any State or Territory of the Commonwealth of Australia or a Government Agency; and(c)requirements and approvals (including conditions) of the Commonwealth of Australia or any State or Territory of the Commonwealth of Australia or a Government Agency that have the force of law;Mediator means is a person:(a)having appropriate qualifications and experience relevant to determining the Dispute;(b)who is agreed by the parties or, failing agreement within 5 Business Days, is nominated at the request of any party by the Institute of Arbitrators and Mediators Australia in accordance with its Mediation and Conciliation Rules; and(c)who does not act, or whose firm does not act, generally for any party;Membership means membership of the Program (being either Perks Membership, Perks+ Membership or VIPerks Membership);Membership Card means either the physical or digital card that is issued by BIG4 to a BIG4 Member which is valid for the Membership Period and identifies the BIG4 Member's Membership in the Program (including the level of Membership);Membership Period means, unless otherwise terminated in accordance with these Terms, the period of time stipulated in clause 2.6 during which a BIG4 Member's Membership is active;Membership Saving means a discount on BIG4 Accommodation made with a BIG4 Holiday Park pursuant to clause 6.1;Perks Membership means the level of membership referred to in clause 2.2(a);Perks+ Membership means the level of membership referred to in clause 2.2(b);Permanent Residents mean individuals who (i) either have Perks+ Membership or VIPerks Membership and (ii) live in a BIG4 Park or are annual residents of a BIG4 Park who maintain a permanent site within a BIG4 Park;Person includes a natural person, partnership, body corporate, association, joint venture, governmental or local authority, and any other body or entity whether incorporated or not;Personal Information has the meaning given to that term in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth);Privacy Law means all Laws relating to the privacy, confidentiality or use of any information about individuals, including the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth);Program means the holiday perks membership program owned and administered by BIG4 under the name "BIG4 Holiday Perks" or such other name as determined by BIG4 from time to time;Terms means these terms and conditions as amended from time to time;VIPerks Membership means the level of membership referred to in clause 2.2(c); andWebsite means the website located at www.BIG4.com.au.
4. Brand PromiseBest Price
Guarantee:The Best Price Guarantee means that BIG4.com.au will offer the best rate at the time of booking for accommodation and sites at the relevant BIG4 Holiday Park, and that no lower rate can be found online for the equivalent accommodation and sites at the same BIG4 Holiday Park with the same check-in and check-out dates and the same booking conditions.Exclusions:1.	Offers not made available to the general public, including but not limited to:1.	Offers to a closed group of members of any club or affiliation, which rate is not generally publicly available through any direct online channel; and2.	Offered for equivalent Accommodation and Sites as part of a package promoted on any online channel with different associated benefits, terms and conditions.2.	Prices quoted on websites which do not take online bookings and payments, including those that re-direct you to big4.com.au for transaction.
3.	Prices are lower as a result of an error by the third-party website.4.	BIG4 is unable to reasonably verify price; or5.	The price is lower due to rates not including mandatory fees, surcharges and taxes.The Best Price Guarantee is not valid for Affiliate parks
.All claims must be made prior to, or within an hour of, check-in
at the relevant BIG4 Holiday Park. In the event of a valid claim from a BIG4 guest that the rate paid on BIG4.com.au does not meet the Best Price Guarantee, BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia will promptly notify the relevant BIG4 Holiday Park of such a claim and provide the BIG4 Holiday Park with the relevant details of the claim. The BIG4 Holiday Park will then adjust the rate for Bookings made by the relevant BIG4 Guest, and prior to, or upon check-out, will offer the BIG4 Guest the Accommodation and Sites for the lower rate and settle the difference between the booked rate and the lower rate.COVID Safe:The COVID Safe brand promises ensure that participating parks have adopted best practice management and health and safety procedures in response to COVID –19. These practises are based on National and State Government directives and Caravan and Camping Industry Association guidelines.
COVID-19 Flexible Booking Policy: Withstanding rights under consumer law, guests will have the option to select a new date for their existing booking or accept a credit valid for up to 12 months should any of the below criteria impact their planned stay:•	You or an immediate family member becomes sick with COVID – 19;•	You are forced into self-isolation;•	You are awaiting the results of a COVID – 19 test; or•	A State Government or Commonwealth Government directive is issued and means you are no longer able to travel to or from your destination. Any difference in booking value will need to be paid direct to the park as per their usual booking terms and conditions (see individual Park page on BIG4.com.au for their specific T&Cs).To request either a change to booking dates or to receive a credit for a future booking in relation to the COVID-19 Flexible Cancellation Policy the customer will need to contact the park direct, contact details can be found on the individual park page on BIG4.com.au. To utilise this policy a guest must:•	Have made their booking on BIG4.com.au, and•	Where requested, provide proof to the park where the booking is held of COVID-19 impact as listed above. Any cancellation which is deemed not applicable to the Flexible Cancellation Policy will need to comply with parks usual terms and conditions. See individual park page on BIG4.com.au for their terms and conditions.
Don’t Stay Don’t Pay:If you are not completely happy with the quality or standard of a BIG4 Park, you can notify our friendly front desk staff who will provide a refund of any money paid. To utilise this policy a guest must:•	Notify park reception in person within an hour of arrival•	Not use any facilities of the accommodation they have booked This promise is only available for bookings made on BIG4.com.auCancelation charges may apply if housekeeping is required.
5. International Site Pass Terms and ConditionsThe BIG4 International Park Pass (“Pass”) is issued by BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd ABN 50 006 437 038 (“BIG4”). The Pass remains the property of BIG4.The Pass may only be purchased by persons situated outside Australia who are not ordinarily resident in Australia ("purchaser") from BIG4 or BIG4's approved agents.The Pass is only valid for, and may only be redeemed within, 12 months of purchase of the Pass (“Validity Period”). Any Pass not fully used within the Validity Period will be void and of no value. None of any unused value, and no part of the Pass's purchase price, will be refunded in those circumstances.The Pass may only be purchased in units of nights stays at participating BIG4 Holiday Park locations in Australia ("Parks"), and may only be purchased in multiples of seven (7) nights.The pass can only be used at BIG4 Holiday Parks. It can not be used at BIG4.com.au Affiliate parksUpon payment of the price for the Pass to BIG4 or BIG4's authorised agent, the Pass must will be issued to the purchaser either by being emailed to the purchaser, which the purchaser must print and retain, or will be made available to the purchaser to collect and retain from one of BIG4's authorised locations in Australia. The purchaser must make the Pass available for redemption in accordance with these terms.Subject to the purchaser making payment for the Pass, and payment not being reversed or cancelled by way of chargeback or such means, the Pass entitles the purchaser to access one powered site at participating Parks (subject to availability and blackout periods) for up to so many nights as are validly remaining on the Pass. BIG4 makes no representation or warranty that any powered site will be available at any Park at any time. BIG4 recommends contacting the relevant Park as early as possible prior to arrival in order to improve the likelihood of a successful booking.The Pass will be valid for up to four (4) people per powered site. Additional people staying on the site will be charged at the extra person charge relevant to that Park.If a person does not purchase, use and retain the Pass in accordance with these terms, BIG4 may cancel the Pass at any time and any unused balance left on the Pass will be forfeited.The Pass must be presented at the Park at time of check-in and payment in order to be redeemed. For each night's stay at a Park where the Pass is produced, the balance of nights available on the Pass will be reduced by one. If the purchaser's stay at a Park exceeds the number of nights left on the Pass's balance at the time of redemption, the purchaser must pay for those nights beyond which the Pass is redeemed in accordance with the Park's usual terms.BIG4 is not responsible for any act or omission of a Park.All persons staying at a Park under the Pass must comply with all terms and conditions of the Park applicable to that stay.The Pass may not be redeemed or exchanged for cash. The Pass is not transferable and cannot be on-sold. If the Pass is lost, stolen or destroyed, BIG4 is not obliged to provide a replacement or refund.Blackout periods apply, which are:Four (4) day Easter Long Weekend (being Good Friday to Easter Monday) for all Parks.The period from the 26 December to 31 January for all parks south of the Tropic of Capricorn.The period from 1 July to 31 July for all parks north of the Tropic of Capricorn.Other Special Event periods as determined by individual BIG4 Parks. Please check with your destination park to see if the Pass is valid for the requested booking date.By purchasing a Pass, the purchaser's personal information will be collected by BIG4 from its agents for the purpose of issuing the Pass, and thereafter from relevant Parks for the purpose of administering the pass. BIG4 will also disclose information of the purchaser to relevant Parks for the purpose of administering the Pass and ensuring compliance with the terms and conditions of the Pass. If the purchaser does not provide this personal information, BIG4 may not be able to administer the Pass. BIG4 may disclose personal information overseas, namely to the country where the purchaser is located in order to issue the purchaser with the Pass.BIG4's privacy policy can be found at www.big4.com.au/privacy-policy. It contains information about how an individual may access the personal information about the individual that is held by BIG4 and seek correction of that information, how an individual may complain about a breach of the Australian Privacy Principles and how BIG4 will deal with such a complaint.In the event of a query or a dispute in relation to the Pass, can contact BIG4 on 1300 738 044 or write to BIG4 Holiday Parks, PO Box 543 Camberwell VIC 3124 or via our website's enquiry form on www.big4.com.au/contactNo agent, servant or representative of BIG4 has authority to alter, modify or waive any terms or conditions of the Pass.The Pass and its terms and conditions will be subject to the laws of Australia, and the courts of Australia will have non-exclusive jurisdiction in respect of any dispute arising thereto.
6. BIG4 Holiday Park Reservations and Tariffs PoliciesReservations Conditions and Cancellation PolicyDepositsGenerally, the deposit is at least the cost of the first night's tariff and must be received by the Holiday Park within 7 days of reserving to confirm your reservation.Check-In TimeCheck-in time is after 2pm. Earlier times may be available on request. Please confirm this with the park at the time of reservation.At the time of reserving please provide the Holiday Park with your estimated time of arrival. Should you be delayed, please advise the park and inform them of your revised arrival time.Free Book-Ahead Service for BIG4 Club MembersBIG4 Holiday Parks offers a Free Book-Ahead Service between Holiday Parks to guarantee your accommodation is confirmed at your next destination. Ask about this service when you next check in at any BIG4 Holiday Park.You simply pay the first night's accommodation or site fees for your next BIG4 Holiday Park as a deposit and you will be immediately given a receipt confirming the arrangements.This deposit is subject to strict cancellation policies. Reservations using this service are subject to site availability and must be made while you are at a BIG4 Holiday Park.CancellationsWhen making a direct reservation with a BIG4 Holiday Park, you acknowledge and agree that all reservations and deposits are accepted by park owners subject to the following cancellation policy guidelines. Any reservations through agents or other third parties may be subject to separate policies and you should check their conditions.We recommend you request cancellation details from your chosen Holiday Park at the time of reservation.As a guideline, most parks have the following policies in place:Low-Season Cancellation PolicyDuring the low season, deposits will only be refunded if the park owner is notified of your cancellation prior to 9am on the day prior to your scheduled arrival. If notice of your cancellation is received after 9am on the day prior to your scheduled arrival the park owner may retain the deposit paid.High or Mid-Season Cancellation PolicyDeposits for reservations made wholly or partially in high and mid-seasons will only be refunded if you notify the park owner of your cancellation at least 60 days prior to your scheduled arrival. If you provide less than the required period of notice of cancellation, your deposit will only be refunded if the category of site or cabin that you booked is able to be resold. Low, mid and high-season details are available on request from each Holiday Park.Early DeparturesMost Holiday Parks do not refund should you cut short your reservation or holiday. For further details please check with your chosen Holiday Park.Failure to Notify of CancellationIf you do not notify the park owner of your cancellation or if you do not arrive by 10am on the day after your scheduled arrival date, your reservation may be cancelled by the park owner without refund of any paid deposit.Group Bookings and Special OffersPlease note the above conditions do not apply to group reservations or reservations that are made pursuant to a ‘Special Offer'. Please check with your chosen Holiday Park for terms and conditions with regard to group reservations or special offers.TariffsThe Tariffs on this website apply to the first two people occupying either accommodation or a site. There is a charge for extra persons. Generally a different tariff applies for adults (persons sixteen years of age and older) and children (persons between the ages of two and fifteen inclusive) and can vary between Holiday Parks for accommodation and sites.Infants under two years of age are free of charge at all BIG4 Holiday Parks. Additional fees may apply for linen or cot hire, which will be advised at the time of reservation.All tariffs on this website represent the charges applicable per night at the relevant Holiday Park. Please note the Tariffs and all other information contained herein is indicative and subject to change without notice. It is essential that you confirm the applicable tariffs and any other special conditions with your chosen Holiday Park at the time of reservation.Tariffs are set by the individual Holiday Parks and may vary from time to time. BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia Pty Ltd obtained the information on this website from each of the individual Holiday Parks listed and is therefore not responsible for the accuracy of any such information.Goods and Service Tax (GST) is included in tariffs listed in this publication.Minimum reservation periods may apply during different seasons and these will vary between parks. Please ask for details.Prices may, but do not always, include the supply of linen and bedding. All Holiday Parks have linen available for hire in conjunction with a cabin booking and this should be arranged prior to your arrival.Because BIG4 Holiday Parks are located throughout Australia, location, weather, and a number of other factors mean the variety and standard of accommodation and facilities could vary from Holiday Park to Holiday Park.Additional Holiday Park InformationMotorhome-Friendly SitesParks displaying the Large Motorhome-Friendly Site symbol can comfortably accommodate a prime towing vehicle and trailer on at least some of their sites. Wider roadways or angled sites will allow access for vehicles with large turning circles. Sites will usually be drive through and fully sewered (or have dump points accessible to large vehicles). Typically, there are a limited number of these sites at Holiday Parks; therefore it is essential to make a reservation confirming the site requirements to ensure availability and suitability with respect to the specific requirements of your vehicle.SullageSullage is available for the removal of grey water from powered/ensuite sites. To guarantee availability, these sites must be reserved.Park Reception HoursOffice hours vary from Holiday Park to Holiday Park. Opening hours are at least from 8am to 5pm Monday to Saturday and 9am to 5pm Sunday, with reception at many Holiday Parks open for longer hours.If you are arriving or departing outside these hours, please contact the Holiday Park to make arrangements for payment and collection of keys. Each Holiday Park has accessible management, 24 hours a day.Key DepositsMany BIG4 Holiday Parks have security access to their amenities blocks and/or boom gate access for your security. Parks may require a deposit at the time of check-in for these passes or keys. The amount of this deposit may vary depending on the system installed.Provided the pass or key is returned at the time of check-out, your deposit will be refunded immediately. There will be an early check-out box available for key returns in the event of early departure before the reception opens. Please check prior to leaving the park.Room ServicingAccommodation is not serviced daily unless specified or arranged separately with the park. Additional charges may apply.
7. BIG4 Privacy PolicyBIG4 Privacy PolicyBIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia PTY Ltd (‘BIG4’, ‘We’ or ‘Us’), at 2/313-317 Burwood Rd, Hawthorn VIC 3122, Australia.We are a data controller and processor, for the purpose of the General Data Protection Regulation GDPR (in countries applicable). BIG4 is responsible for the controlling and processing of your personal information as noted below.This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or register on our website
(The Site).We respect our customers’ privacy and for that reason we will manage our customers’ personal information in accordance with our privacy policy as stated below.By using or registering on The Site you confirm that you are agree to the BIG4 Privacy and cookie policy detailed below. Personal InformationThe type of personal information we collect includes:Your name and contact details;Payment and transaction details/history;Details regarding participation in BIG4's Perks membership program:Details/history of preferences, interests and behaviour relating to transactions, products, services and activity with our digital services:Your computer IP address when visiting our website;Records of your communications and interactions with us, such as details of your previous dealings with us or any of the BIG4 Parks; andFinancial information (e.g. for invoicing and payments of services, products and Loyalty Club membership or personal credit information when you make payments to us).We will treat this information as personal information. Visiting the Site and Registering your detailsWhen you visit The Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse The Site, we collect information about the individual site pages you view, the websites or search terms that referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site.We will collect and store your personal information via the following methods:Provided by you through registration process on the Site; orProvided by you through mail or phone registration process.We will treat this information as personal information.Please note that we do not store any payment details, such as credit card information. Information about other peopleWhere you provide us with information about other people (e.g. people you're travelling with) you must have consent to do so. If we collect personal information about an individual from you (e.g. to send a BIG4 Gift Voucher), we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that the individual will be or has been made aware of this privacy policy and:Our identity and how to contact us;that he or she can access the information;the purpose for which we have collected the information;the organisations or types of organisations that we usually disclose the information to;Any law that requires particular information to be collected;The main consequences (if any) for the individual if all or part of the information is not provided; andWhether any personal information is likely to be disclosed overseas, and if practicable, notify the recipient countries.We will treat this information as personal information. CookiesCookies are data files that are automatically placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. Type of CookiesCookies we use in the Site fall into the following two categories:Essential cookies, these are cookies originate from our Site:Session cookies are automatically deleted at the end of each browsing session, typically when the web browser is closed; andPersistent cookies remain until the expiry date and time set by the web server. They can be manually deleted by You.Essential cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The Site cannot function properly without these cookies.3rd party cookies originate from a domain that is different to the Site visited.We will treat this information as personal information. Turning cookies on or offYou have a number of options when it comes to receiving cookies. You can set your browser either to reject all cookies, to allow only ‘trusted’ sites to send them, or to accept only those cookies from websites you are currently using.We recommend that you do not block cookies from BIG4. We use the data stored in cookies for functionality within the Site and to improve the experience you receive on the Site.If you prefer not to receive cookies then you accept that you will be unable to set up a user account or register for some of the services we offer; both rely on cookies to function effectively.Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser Log filesLog files gather information and track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.We will treat this information as personal information. Using and Disclosing Your Personal InformationWe, use the personal information you provide for the following purposes:Register your details with BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia;Record your booking or other purchase with BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia;To maintain a database of current and past guests;Subscribing to our email newsletterAdditionally, we use the information within log files to help us screen for potential risk and breaches (in particular, IP addresses), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). Advertising on the SiteWhen the Site contains links to a variety of advertising and third-party website sources, BIG4 has no control over the content or privacy policy practices of such sites and encourage our users to review the privacy policies of such sites before engaging in any activity with them. Disclosing and Sharing your personal informationWe may disclose your information with the following parties:With our Parks, to verify your membership details, confirm an accommodation booking, Gift Voucher or prize and to provide you with services;With third-party contractors or partners who are engaged to perform services on our behalf such as:Sending you a copy of the BIG4 Guide;Issuing or sending you BIG4 membership or Gift Cards;Marketing tools that are used to optimise and improve BIG4 customer experience or creating marketing campaigns;Technology suppliers such as our Australian hosting provider;All these parties are bound by our mutual non-disclosure agreement that controls the use and disclosure of personal information and prohibits any sharing of information with other entities without express written consent from BIG4.With legal authorities for any criminal investigation to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.We use analytical tools to help us understand how our customers use The Site and optimise the user experience on The Site.We may also share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors our website receives or the most popular parks and destinations. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services.We will not sell your personal information to marketing bodies without your consent. Direct MarketingWhen you provide your personal details to us, you consent to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes (unless you have already opted out of marketing, or until you opt out). Personal information may be disclosed for marketing purposes to an organisation or people who assist in our direct marketing, for example an external mail house.From time to time, we may contact you with information about products and services offered by us and our related entities and our business partners, that we think may be of interest to you. When we contact you it may be by email or SMS.You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the marketing e-mails we send you or via My Account page on The Site. Protecting, Storing and Disposing Personal InformationData Storage and ProtectionYour data is stored and protected in accordance to industry better practices in BIG4 securely hosted Data Centres in Australia.Our security practices and processes to store and handle this data is regularly reviewed by independent third-party security firms and optimised in accordance to their recommendations. We regularly monitor The Site using technology tools to help us identify, protect, detect, respond and recover from any malicious activities on The Site that may impact Your data.Your personal information is stored in our secure data centres in Australia. Data RetentionWhen you register your information through The Site, we will keep your Information for our records as follows:Until you request us to delete this information.If a Park requests us to delete this informationAs required by our legal and regulatory requirementsIf data cannot be deleted due to integrity of past records (for example historical booking) then personal data will be anonymised or de-identified. Your RightsAs a BIG4 customer, You have the following rights in regards of your data:Request details about the data we hold about youRequest details about how the data is stored, handled and processedRequest changes and/or modification to the dataRequest deleting/de-identifying your detailsRequest to 'opt out' from receiving direct marketing communications.If you would like to exercise any of the above, please contact us through the contact information below. Changes to this policyWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. If you continue to access or use our services after notified changes have come into effect, you will have agreed to the revised policy. Contact UsIf you have any concerns, queries, disputes or complaints about our privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact BIG4's Privacy Officer on:Phone: 03 9811 9300 orEmail: privacy@big4.com.auPost: Privacy Officer, BIG4 Holiday Parks of Australia, PO Box 543, Camberwell 3124, Australia Complaints and further informationIf you have any disputes or complaints, our privacy officer will attend to them and may request that you put your dispute or complaint in writing. Our privacy officer will investigate any dispute or complaint and respond to you within a reasonable time.This privacy policy may be amended or updated to ensure that we maintain the highest standards.All BIG4 Holiday Parks are owned and operated by Franchisees who are individual businessmen and businesswomen. For their individual BIG4 Member Park privacy policies, please contact them directly.For information about privacy generally, or if your concerns are not resolved to your satisfaction, you may contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at www.oaic.gov.au and on 1300 363 992
Map View
Make a Booking
Pet Friendly Parks
New South Wales
Northern Territory
Queensland
South Australia
Tasmania
Forgot Member Number or Password?
Member Benefits
BIG4 Gift Cards
Contact us
Contact the BIG4 National Support Office via our contact us page.
BIG4 Gift Cards
Inspire someone you know to get out and explore this beautiful country of ours. Start them on their way by surprising them with a BIG4 Gift Card.
BIG4 Holiday Perks+ Membership
Enjoy 10% savings (up to $50) on every BIG4 holiday plus heaps more! Learn more.
*For more information on BIG4's Price Guarantee please see our Terms & Conditions
